footballlocks.com 2011-01-01

# FootballLOCKS.com: Privacy Policy for online NFL pick purchases at FootballLOCKS.com.

**Football _LOCKS_.com knows that your privacy is important to you and Football _LOCKS_.com recognizes and respects your right to maintain your privacy on the web and beyond. **

Football _LOCKS_.com will not share private information about you with any third party unless forced to do so by law or legal proceedings, or unless Football _LOCKS_.com has reason to believe you are causing interference or injury to Football _LOCKS_.com, its agents, principals, representatives, service providers, advertisers or affiliates in which case such information would be used for legal purposes. 

All credit card transactions for Football _LOCKS_.com are processed securely, and your credit card number is not stored on any computer connected to the internet. 

The e-mail address you provide in connection with billing of Football _LOCKS_.com picks will be used to provide you with a receipt for your records as well as to provide you with any make up NFL picks that may be due to you in the event of a game invalidating occurrence as described in our general policies. 

If you have subscribed for [NFL pick e-mail notification,](http://www.footballlocks.com/notification.shtml) the e-mail address you provide will be used for NFL pick e-mail notification, updates of pick records, special offers and replacement picks only. You may opt out of Football _LOCKS_.com NFL pick e-mail notification at any time by revisiting the e-mail sign up page. 

Football _LOCKS_.com may share aggregate demographic information about users to advertisers and others for the purposes of customizing ads for the site. For example, Football _LOCKS_.com might say that x% of users are of a certain gender, but no personal information will be revealed. 

Football _LOCKS_.com does not and will not link personal information about you to your IP address (your IP address is the number that's automatically assigned to your computer when you're on the net) unless its for legal purposes or Football _LOCKS_.com feels it's necessary to enforce its policies, protect its interests, and protect the interest of our customers. 

Football _LOCKS_.com makes use of cookies so that you do not have to re-enter certain order information when purchasing a pick. Football _LOCKS_.com does not store your credit card information using cookies or any other method. 

Football _LOCKS_.com only transmits cookies over a secure server connection. 

Football _LOCKS_.com may contain links to other sites. If you click on such a link, these other sites may make use of cookies (third party cookies). Football _LOCKS_.com is not responsible for the privacy, the practices, or the content of any such web sites. 

By using the Football _LOCKS_.com web site you are consenting to the privacy policy as described. Football _LOCKS_.com reserves the right to change its privacy policy at any time and in the event that a change has occurred changes will be posted on this page.
